[{"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "In 2000, microbes were found at the South Pole.", "correct_answer": "True", "incorrect_answers": ["False"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "The White House rejected Louisiana governor Kathleen Blancos request to declare an emergency before Hurricane Katrina had struck.", "correct_answer": "False", "incorrect_answers": ["True"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Ava and Mia were two of the wives of which famous persons?", "correct_answer": "Frank Sinatra", "incorrect_answers": ["Henry VIII", "Artie Shaw", "Louis XIV"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "In 2006 Chris Gardner started working for what firm?", "correct_answer": "No firm", "incorrect_answers": ["Martin, Penny  and Forbes", "His own firm", "Goldman Sachs"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Which EU member is divided into a Greek and a Turkish part?", "correct_answer": "Cyprus", "incorrect_answers": ["Greece", "Slovenia", "Bulgaria"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "This gland, located in the base of the human skull, is the central gland in the endocrine regulation and is as large as a pea.", "correct_answer": "The pituitary gland", "incorrect_answers": ["The thyroid gland", "The thymus", "Erbers gland"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Who is the first actor/actress to win an Oscar for playing a member of the opposite sex?", "correct_answer": "Linda Hunt", "incorrect_answers": ["Felicity Huffman", "Dustin Hoffman", "Nathan Lane"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Lanugo is a term related to hair. What does it mean?", "correct_answer": "Fine hair that grows on fetuses", "incorrect_answers": ["A parasite that feeds on human hair", "A medical condition connected with loss of hair", "A type of grease that Eskimos use to keep their hair conditioned"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "What do Louis, Billy Ray, Coleman and Ophelia do with their new found wealth at the end of the movie Trading Places?", "correct_answer": "All four of them retire to a tropical island", "incorrect_answers": ["All four of them go their separate ways", "All four of them are prosecuted for insider trading", "All four of them donate their money to a homeless shelter"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "This famous writer, whose house was at 17 Gough Square in London, said: When a man is tired of London, he is tired of life, for there is in London all life can afford.", "correct_answer": "Dr Samuel Johnson", "incorrect_answers": ["Charles Dickens", "Thomas Chestre", "Tomas John Dibdin"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "What type of chicken is used for the preparation of the traditional French meal Coq au vin?", "correct_answer": "Older rooster", "incorrect_answers": ["Young rooster", "Hen which has just begun to lay eggs", "Older hen"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "In the beginning of the movie Steel Magnolias, what was Drum shooting at?", "correct_answer": "birds", "incorrect_answers": ["bees", "squirrels", "moles"]}]